<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ivy Markwell</title>
    <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ivy Markwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ivymarkwell.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Server Side Rendered HTML Using Phoenix Liveview</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/posts/server-side-rendered-html-using-phoenix-liveview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/posts/server-side-rendered-html-using-phoenix-liveview/</guid>
      <description>Server-side rendered HTML using Phoenix LiveView “LiveView” television
After attending the 2019 Lone Star Elixir conference in Austin, Texas and hearing the release of Phoenix LiveView announced, I decided I wanted to jump on the train of dabbling in LiveView. At the time, a lot of the examples being released were mini games which is what initially inspired me to recreate Minesweeper! After reading this you should understand what LiveView is, know some of the advantages and disadvantages of server side rendered HTML, and have an insight into how I used LiveView to build a clone of Minesweeper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Custom User Confirmation Modal With the React Router Prompt</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/posts/creating-a-custom-user-confirmation-modal-with-the-react-router-prompt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/posts/creating-a-custom-user-confirmation-modal-with-the-react-router-prompt/</guid>
      <description>Writing a custom UserConfirmation modal with the React Router Prompt A person up in arms about wanting custom modals in their Prompt component
This is a short walkthrough on how to use React-Router’s v5 Promptcomponent to replace the built in user confirmation window object with your own custom UserConfirmation modal.
There is another really good article about blocking the navigation to prevent the default modal so that we can render our own custom component instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create and Deploying Your First Hugo Site to Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/posts/create-and-deploying-your-first-hugo-site-to-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/posts/create-and-deploying-your-first-hugo-site-to-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>Creating and deploying your first Hugo site to Github pages A local duck I photographed recently
This is a comprehensive guide for creating your first static site using Hugo and hosting it on GitHub pages.
Creating your site First, make sure you have Hugo installed on your machine.
Now you can run these commands to make your first site.
And there you go! You’ve created your first Hugo site. I mean, there’s nothing in it, but still!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/</guid>
      <description>Photography Most pictures are taken with the Canon EOS Rebel T6i Digital SLR but some pictures I wanted to share are just taken from my iPhone.
 2020 Tootie May 11     2019 London, UK Nov 9   Code Mesh LDN Nov 6   Guanajuato, Mexico Aug 2   Guanajuato, Mexico Aug 1   San Miguel de Allende, Mexico Jul 31   León, Mexico Jul 30   Cuerámaro, Mexico Jul 28   Pecan Street Festival May 4   Lonestar Elixir Mar 3     2018 Cardiff, UK Sep 9   Cardiff, UK Sep 8   Liverpool, UK - Cardiff, UK Sep 7   Liverpool, UK Sep 6   Liverpool, UK Sep 5   Barcelona, Spain Sep 4   Barcelona, Spain Sep 3   Barcelona, Spain Sep 2   Barcelona, Spain Sep 1   Cinco De Mayo May 6   Heidelberg Project Apr 22       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 21:26:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description> Guanajuato, Mexico
 I&#39;m a software engineer in Austin, Texas.
I love to game, travel and have recently gotten into photography. In the past few years I&#39;ve traveled to, in alphabetical order: Canada, Iceland, Mexico, Spain, Sweden, the UK and hopefully many more to come. If you go to my photography section right now you can find pictures from 2018 and onward.
Feel free to reach out!
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>