<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photography on Ivy Markwell</title>
    <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photography on Ivy Markwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 17:19:26 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Portraits</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/portraits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 17:19:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/portraits/</guid>
      <description>Some of the people and non-people I&#39;ve encountered and gotten to take a couple pictures of.
 Nico Vergara
     Tootie
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Kingdom Day 5</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/united-kingdom-day-five/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:14:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/united-kingdom-day-five/</guid>
      <description>My last day of my trip was one of the most eventful. I took a free bus to the Brecon National Park an hour north of Cardiff. I ended up getting off at the wrong place with a group of five other people in the middle of the park with no cell service. I was able to eventually catch another bus on the side of the road to the small city I was going to and it was beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Kingdom Day 4</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/united-kingdom-day-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 23:57:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/united-kingdom-day-four/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed Cardiff a lot more than I did Liverpool. One of the best things I did was visiting the Cardiff Castle. I spent the day going to the docks, just like in Liverpool and checking out the local bars. I even met someone in a bar who was from the next city over from me in Michigan!
                             </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Kingdom Day 3</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/united-kingdom-day-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 23:57:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/united-kingdom-day-three/</guid>
      <description>I took a train from Liverpool to Cardiff. It was so much better than I even thought it could have been.
             </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Kingdom Day 2</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/united-kingdom-day-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 23:20:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/united-kingdom-day-two/</guid>
      <description>I wasn&#39;t in Liverpool very long. My second day was my only full day there. I spent most of the my day going to museums and exploring. I went to the Merseyside Maritime Museum and saw the docks. Later I went to the world museum, and circled back around to my hotel to see a local graffiti alley then ended the day by going to a cat cafe.
                                       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Kingdom Day 1</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/united-kingdom-day-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 21:48:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/united-kingdom-day-one/</guid>
      <description>I arrived to Liverpool, UK in the afternoon and so most of my first day was spent getting my nails done and drinking coffee amongst other things.
         </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spain Day 4</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/spain-day-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:22:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/spain-day-four/</guid>
      <description>My fourth day in Barcelona was a lot more relaxed. I only went to the beach and to my tattoo appointment for my daisies.
                     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spain Day 3</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/spain-day-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 23:53:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/spain-day-three/</guid>
      <description>This is the day I forgot my camera in my hotel. So unfortunately all the pictures that I took during my air balloon ride were on my iPhone 7. Overall it was really amazing, still scary, but a great experience. I met a really nice Chinese couple who were honeymooning through Spain along with the staff from Ballooning Barcelona. Afterwards, I walked to Park Güell and through the northern part of Barcelona and finished at a really nice sushi resturant called Robata.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spain Day 2</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/spain-day-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 22:34:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/spain-day-two/</guid>
      <description>My second day in Spain I mostly spent climbing Monserrat. I took the Aeri de Monserrat cable car early in the morning to the Montserrat Monastery. I spent about an hour to two hours climbing to Sant Jeroni with a girl I met from Quebec, Canada. I went back into Barcelona in the evening to eat and relax and on the way back to my hotel I ran into two little girls playing a game of pretending to sell toys on the street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spain Day 1</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/spain-day-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 23:19:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/spain-day-one/</guid>
      <description>My first day in Barcelona, Spain! I started the morning by going to the La Boqueria, a local market in the center of the city. I walked around and went to the Catalonoia Square where you could feed pigeons and then headed to a reservation I had at Niño Viejo. Afterwards I went to Plaça d&#39;Espanya and Museu Nacional d&#39;Art de Catalunya. On my way back to my hotel to get ready for a local meet up I was attending, I met José and his chickens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinco De Mayo</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/cinco-de-mayo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 19:53:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/cinco-de-mayo/</guid>
      <description>Cinco de Mayo is the celebration of the victory of the Battle of Puebla on May 5th, 1862. Detroit holds a yearly parade in Mexican Town where they drive down the streets and throw candy for the kids.
                   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heidelberg Project</title>
      <link>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/heidelberg-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 13:41:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivymarkwell.github.io/photography/heidelberg-project/</guid>
      <description>The Heidelberg Project is an artistic protest done by Tyree Guyton after the deterioration of Heidelberg street during the Detroit 1967 riots.
               </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>